Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Charters Collections, 1899-2014 IBT0087
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Charters Collections
1899-2014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0087
13.5 Linear Feet 9 oversize flat document boxes
This collection contains charters of International Brotherhood of Teamsters local unions, joint councils, and other affiliated groups.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
Organized into 2 series: IBT Local Charters and IBT Affiliate Charters. Items within the series are arranged by local number and then by date. Series 1, Boxes 8 and 9 were processed at a later date and are thus arranged individually by local number separate from the rest of the collection.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters,2017 (2017.70)
Scope and Contents
This collection contains charters of International Brotherhood of Teamsters local unions, joint councils, and other affiliated groups. Most charters are original. Some charters are mounted or framed. Charters vary in condition, with some charters having sustained damage with age.
Biographical / Historical
The International Brotherhood of Teamsters issues charters to its local unions and joint councils. This is the official recognition of the affiliated body allowing the local or joint council to undertake collective bargaining, organizing and dues collection. Each charter displays the number of the body, the names of the charter members, date of affiliation, and official title which often designates jurisdiction. Each charter is signed by the General President and General Secretary-Treasurer. Charters can be revoked by IBT headquarters.
International Brotherhood of Teamsters; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Charters
- IBT Local Charters, 1899-2014; Series 1
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains charters from International Brotherhood of Teamsters Union Locals.
  Arrangement
  Items in this series are arranged by local union number and then chronologically.
  - Local 4, Newspaper, Magazine, and Electronic Media Workers, Prepress, Press, Packaging and Distribution, and Miscellanous Publishing Workers, Minnesota, April 23, 2003 (Box 1, Item 1)
  - Local 4, Newspaper, Magazine, and Electronic Media Workers, Prepress, Press, Packaging and Distribution, and Miscellanous Publishing Workers, Minnesota and Iowa, August 13, 2004 (Box 1, Item 2)
  - Local 9, International Telegraph Employees, United States west of the Rocky Mountains excluding Hawaii, November 15, 1966 (Box 1, Item 3)
  - Local 10, International Telegraph Employees, United States west of the Ricky Mountains including Hawaii, November 15, 1966 (Box 1, Item 4)
  - Local 12, Stroh Brewery Workers, Fogelsville, Pennsylvania, September 30, 1985 (Box 1, Item 5)
  - Local 12, Pabst Brewery Company, Fogelsville, Pennsylvania, May 22, 2001 (Box 1, Item 6)
  - Local 13, Teamsters Construction Workers, Colorado, February 9, 1981 (Box 1, Item 7)
  - Local 14, General Sales Drivers, Delivery Drivers and Helpers, Las Vegas, Nevada, December 20, 1955 (Box 1, Item 8)
  - Local 14, Public Sector, Las Vegas, Nevada, October 18, 2005 (Box 1, Item 9)
  - Local 15, Mailing Room, Printing Offices, and Mailing Agencies Employees, Northern California, March 11, 1987 (Box 1, Item 10)
  - Local 17, Teamsters, Denver, Colorado, April 1, 1943 (Box 1, Item 11)
  - Local 26, Teamsters, Danville, Illinois, June 17, 1944 (Box 1, Item 12)
  - Local 28, General Drivers, Warehousemen, and Helpers, South Carolina, February 1, 1970 (Box 1, Item 13)
  - Local 31, Teamsters, Vancouver and General Jurisdiction of Prince George and Yukon Territory, Canada, September 16, 1992 (Box 1, Item 14)
  - Local 47, Teamsters, Fort Worth, Texas, May 15, 1941 (Box 1, Item 15)
  - Local 41, Teamsters, Missouri and Kansas, October 27, 1998 (Box 1, Item 16)
  - Local 46, Teamsters, Peru, Illinois, December 1, 1940 (Box 1, Item 17)
  - Joint Council 46, Buffalo, New York, April 22, 1949 (Box 1, Item 18)
  - Local 46, Brewery Workers and Delivery Employees, New York, March 23, 1977 (Box 1, Item 19)
  - Local 48, State County, Municipal, and University Employees, Maine, April 6, 1978 (Box 1, Item 20)
  - Local 50, Teamsters, Bellville Illinois, July 26, 1899; Series 1
  - Local 50, Teamsters, Illinois, June 26, 1980 (Box 1, Item 21)
  - Local 55, Metropolitan Police Patrolman's Union, Massachusetts, February 23, 1977 (Box 1, Item 22)
  - Local 56, General Drivers, Dairy Products Employees and Helpers, Sheboygan, Wisconsin, August 3, 1942 (Box 1, Item 23)
  - Local 57, Teamsters, Oregon, April 6th, 1978 (Box 1, Item 24)
  - Local 59, Teamsters, Massachusetts, May 8, 1968 (Box 1, Item 25)
  - Local 61, Teamsters, West North Carolina, September 12, 1996 (Box 1, Item 26)
  - Joint Council 65, Springfield, Illinois, April 7, 1949 (Box 1, Item 27)
  - Local 69, Quebec Teamsters, Northeast Quebec, February 8, 1979 (Box 1, Item 28)
  - Local 70, Teamsters, Alameda County, California, July 9, 1984 (Box 1, Item 29)
  - Local 73, Industrial and Allied Employees, Ohio, June 6, 1969 (Box 1, Item 30)
  - Local 86, Teamsters' Industrial Union, South Carolina, August 2, 1971 (Box 1, Item 31)
  - Local 87, Teamsters, Kern County, California, May 21, 1973 (Box 1, Item 32)
  - Local 91, Teamsters, East Ontario, January 16, 1978 (Box 1, Item 33)
  - Local 96, Teamsters, California, January 13, 1948 (Box 1, Item 34)
  - Local 99, Louisville Mailers Union, Louisville, Kentucky, July 1, 1987 (Box 1, Item 35)
  - Local 105, Ice, Storage, and Scrap Materials Employees, Ohio and Kentucky, January 23, 1951 (Box 1, Item 36)
  - Local 105, Ice, Storage, and Scrap Materials Employees, Ohio and Kentucky, February 8, 1956 (Box 1, Item 37)
  - Local 106, Transport Drivers, Quebec, October 12, 1973 (Box 1, Item 38)
  - Local 114, Bakery, Cracker, Pie, and Yeast Drivers, Cincinnati, Ohio, December 1, 1940 (Box 1, Item 39)
  - Local 116, Teamsters, North Dakota and Minnesota, September 21, 1945 (Box 1, Item 40)
  - Local 116, Teamsters, North Dakota and Minnesota, May 26, 1992 (Box 1, Item 41)
  - Local 118, Teamsters, Rochester, New York, December 1, 1940 (Box 1, Item 42)
  - Local 124, Teamsters Steel Workers and Special Commodity Haulers, Detroit, Michigan, August 20, 1990 (Box 1, Item 43)
  - Local 132, Chemical, Energy, and Allied Workers, Ontario, February 7, 1979 (Box 1, Item 44)
  - Local 135, Teamsters, Indianapolis, Indiana, December 1, 1940 (Box 1, Item 45)
  - Local 135, Teamsters of Indianapolis, Indiana and Airline Employees of Indiana, September 5, 2001 (Box 1, Item 46)
  - Local 137, Teamsters, California, October 13, 1994 (Box 1, Item 47)
  - Local 138, Teamsters, New York, New York, April 25, 1927 (Box 1, Item 48)
  - Local 144, Teamsters, Indiana and Illinois, April 6, 1966 (Box 1, Item 49)
  - Local 154, Teamsters Chemical, Energy, and Allied Workers, Ontario, February 7, 1979 (Box 1, Item 50)
  - Local 155, Movie Production, Trade Shows, and Related Industries, British Columbia and the Yukon Territories, October 21, 1987 (Box 1, Item 51)
  - Local 156, Taxi Cab Drivers, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, July 3, 1934 (Box 1, Item 52)
  - Local 158, Allied Trades and Bulk Plant Workers, Amusement Park Workers, and Industrial Workers, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, January 26, 1962 (Box 1, Item 53)
  - Local 161, Transportation Checkers, Receivers, and Clerical Workers, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, October 20, 1955 (Box 1, Item 54)
  - Local 178, Chemical and Allied Workers, Quebec, October 24, 1978 (Box 1, Item 55)
  - Local 182, Teamsters, Utica, New York, December 1, 1940 (Box 1, Item 56)
  - Local 182, Teamsters, Utica, New York, January 15, 2004 (Box 1, Item 57)
  - Local 190, Teamsters, Billings, Montana, December 1, 1940 (Box 1, Item 58)
  - Local 193, Teamsters, Indianapolis, Indiana, August 4, 1942 (Box 1, Item 59)
  - Local 194, Bakery Drivers and Salesmen, Newark, New Jersey, February 27, 1940 (Box 1, Item 60)
  - Local 194, Bakery Drivers and Salesmen and Frozen Products Drivers, Newark, New Jersey, December 7, 1954 (Box 1, Item 61)
  - Local 196, United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers, Memphis, Tennessee, January 2, 1969 (Box 1, Item 62)
  - Local 202, Produce Purveyors, Fresh and Frozen Fruits and Vegetables, Processed Fish Drivers, Warehousemen, and Helpers, New York, New York, December 9, 1954 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - Local 202, Produce Purveyors, Fresh and Frozen Fruits and Vegetables, Processed Fish Drivers, Warehousemen, and Helpers, and Allied Chemical and Surgical Workers, New York, New York, March 6, 2002 (Box 2, Item 2)
  - Local 202, Produce Purveyors, Fresh and Frozen Fruits and Vegetables, Processed Fish Drivers, Warehousemen, and Helpers, and Allied Chemical and Surgical Workers, Butter, Egg, and Cheese Drivers, Inspectors, Candlers, Graders, Processors, Packers, Shippers, Employees working in the Fresh-cut Flower Industry, Greater New York Area, New York, September 10, 2008 (Box 2, Item 3)
  - Local 206, Warehousemen, Portland, Oregon, December 1, 1940 (Box 2, Item 4)
  - Local 213, Teamsters, British Columbia and Yukon Territory, March 21, 1985 (Box 2, Item 5)
  - Local 217, General Teamsters, West of Tennessee River to Shelby County Line, January 14, 1980 (Box 2, Item 6)
  - Local 227, Bakery Salesmen, Seattle, Washington, December 1, 1940 (Box 2, Item 7)
  - Local 228, Food Process Workers, Warehousemen, and Helpers, Sacramento, California, November 27, 1957 (Box 2, Item 8)
  - Local 228, Food Process Workers, Warehousemen, and Helpers, Sacramento, California, November 29, 1989 (Box 2, Item 9)
  - Local 228, Food Process Workers, Warehousemen, and Helpers in Sacramento and Public, Professional, and Medical Employees of Yolo, Nevada, Placer, El Dorado, Alpine, Mono, Stanislaus, Maiposa, and Merced, California, October 13, 1994 (Box 2, Item 10)
  - Local 230, Ready-Mix, Building Supply, Hydro and Construction Drivers, Warehousemen, and Helpers, Ontario, September 19, 1968 (Box 2, Item 11)
  - Local 232, Petroleum Drivers, Helpers, and Allied Employees, Northeastern New York State, August 20, 1954 (Box 2, Item 12)
  - Local 234, Teamsters Public Employees of Greater Cleveland and Vicinity, Greater Cleveland Area, Ohio, April 1, 1984 (Box 2, Item 13)
  - Local 239, General Automotive, Electronics, Synthetic and Specialty Products Drivers, Helpers, and Warehousemen, New York, New York, September 17, 1954 (Box 2, Item 14)
  - Local 243, Van Drivers, Furniture Handlers, Warehousemen and Packers, Detroit, Michigan, December 1, 1940 (Box 2, Item 15)
  - Local 247, Building Material, Coal, Individual Truck Owner Drivers, Drivers and Helpers, Wayne, Macomb, Washtenaw, Monroe, and Oakland, Michigan, April 13, 1972 (Box 2, Item 16)
  - Local 246, Dairy Delivery and Plant Processing, Court Personnel, Bank, Appliance Service, Pharmacist, Public Law Enforcement Personnel and Related Clerical Employees, Bakery, Laundry, and Allied Sales Drivers, Nurses Aides, Senior Nurses Aides, Dietary Aides, Maintenance Aides, and Housekeeping and Laundry Aides, Washington, DC, March 13, 1998 (Box 2, Item 17)
  - Local 251, Teamsters, Providence, Rhode Island, April 19, 1984 (Box 2, Item 18)
  - Local 251, Teamsters, Rhode Island, September 7, 2000 (Box 2, Item 19)
  - Local 251, Teamsters, Rhode Island and Southern Massachusetts, February 16, 2005 (Box 2, Item 20)
  - Local 261, Teamsters, Beaver, Lawrence, and Southern Mercer Counties, Pennsylvania, June 29, 1954 (Box 2, Item 21)
  - Local 265, Chauffeurs, San Francisco, California, December 1, 1940 (Box 2, Item 22)
  - Local 268, Aluminum Drivers, Helpers, and Warehousemen, The Identitcal Jurisdiction to Joint Council 73, New Jersey, December 31, 1964 (Box 2, Item 23)
  - Local 273, Drivers and Employees of the Petroleum Industry, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, July 16, 1946 (Box 2, Item 24)
  - Local 274, Soft Drink Workers, Eastern Alberta, October 1, 1967 (Box 2, Item 25)
  - Local 277, Egg Industry Employees and Fresh-Cut Flower Industry Employees, Greater New York Area, New York, March 15, 1968 (Box 2, Item 26)
  - Local 283, Cylinder Gas, Petroleum, Distillery, Auto Service and Accessory Drivers, Maintenance, Mechanics, Helpers, and Inside Employees, Detroit, Michigan, August 2, 1982 (Box 2, Item 27)
  - Local 291, Construction, Building Materials and Miscellaneous Workers, Alameda County, California, January 16, 1978 (Box 2, Item 28)
  - Local 294, Team Drivers, Albany, New York, December 1, 1940 (Box 2, Item 29)
  - Local 294, Teamsters, Albany, New York, June 17, 2009 (Box 2, Item 30)
  - Local 296, Sales Delivery Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers in Santa Clara and San Benito Counties and Newspaper, Magazine, and Periodical Circulators and Drivers in Santa Clara, Alameda, Contra Costa, and San Benito Counties, California, August 24, 1988 (Box 2, Item 31)
  - Local 298, Teamsters, Michigan City, Indiana, December 1, 1940 (Box 2, Item 32)
  - Local 300 Teamsters Warehousemen and Sugar Factory Workers, Greeley, Ft. Morgan, Colorado and Bayard, Mtchell, Scottsbluff, Nebraska, February 19, 1991 (Box 2, Item 33)
  - Local 303, Soft Drink and Mineral Water Workers, St. Louis, Missouri, December 6, 1973 (Box 2, Item 34)
  - Local 307, Teamsters, Wyoming, April 12, 1955 (Box 2, Item 35)
  - Local 311, Petroleum, Construction, Tankline Drivers, Yeast, Soft Drink Workers and Driver-Salesmen, Amusement and Vneding Service Men and Allied Workers, Baltimore, Maryland, May 2, 1983 (Box 2, Item 36)
  - Local 312, Teamsters, Chester, Pennsylvania, December 1, 1940 (Box 2, Item 37)
  - Local 324, Soft Drink Workers, Ontario, June 1, 1957 (Box 2, Item 38)
  - Local 326, Brewery Employees, Ontario, February 1, 1955 (Box 2, Item 39)
  - Local 327, Teamsters, Nashville, Tennessee, December 1, 1940 (Box 2, Item 40)
  - Local 328, Teamsters, Wisconsin and Michigan, January 18, 1950 (Box 2, Item 41)
  - Local 330, Brewery Products Division, Winnipeg, Manitoba, October 22, 1956 (Box 2, Item 42)
  - Local 330, Brewery and Soft Drink Workers, Winnipeg, Manitoba, March 18, 1958 (Box 2, Item 43)
  - Local 330, Branch no. 2, Minnedosa Distillery Workers, Minnedosa, Manitoba, January 2, 1969 (Box 2, Item 44)
  - Local 331, Teamsters, Atlantic City, New Jersey, January 15, 1985 (Box 2, Item 45)
  - Local 331, Teamsters, Atlantic City, New Jersey, April 1, 2010 (Box 2, Item 46)
  - Local 332, General Drivers and Helpers, Flint, Michigan, December 1, 1940 (Box 2, Item 47)
  - Local 333, Brewery, Yeast, Soft Drink Workers and Driver-Salesmen, Amusement, and Vending Service Men, Baltimore, Maryland, April 15, 1957 (Box 2, Item 48)
  - Local 335, Bakery, Dry Cleaning, Laundry, and Miscellaneous Sales Routemen and Helpers, Greater Kansas City, Missouri, November 19, 1962 (Box 3, Item 1)
  - Local 336, Milk, Ice Cream Drivers and Dairy Employees, Cleveland, Ohio, December 1, 1940 (Box 3, Item 2)
  - Local 339, Teamsters, St. Clair, Sanilac, Huron, Tuscola, and Macomb Counties, Michigan, February 24, 1966 (Box 3, Item 3)
  - Local 340, Teamsters, Portland, Maine, December 1, 1940 (Box 3, Item 4)
  - Local 344, Sales and Service Industry, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, June 25, 1974 (Box 3, Item 5)
  - Local 346, General Drivers, Dairy Employees, Wareousemen, Helpers, and Inside Employees, Minnesota, September 27, 1976 (Box 3, Item 6)
  - Local 358, Des Moines Mailers Union, Iowa, April 28, 1987 (Box 3, Item 7)
  - Local 360, Houston Mailers Union, Texas, March 3, 1987 (Box 3, Item 8)
  - Local 363, Industrial and Allied Trades Workers, New York, New York, January 14, 1974 (Box 3, Item 9)
  - Local 373, General Local, Fort Smith, Arkansas, July 13, 1948 (Box 3, Item 10)
  - Local 373, General Local, Fort Smith, Michigan, May 26, 2000 (Box 3, Item 11)
  - Local 376, Automobile Drivers, Demonstrators, Auto Service Department and Industrial Employees, Detroit, Michigan, April 26, 1978 (Box 3, Item 12)
  - Local 377, Teamsters, Youngstown, Ohio, December 1, 1940 (Box 3, Item 13)
  - Local 379, Excavating, Building Material, Teamsters, Chauffeurs, and Helpers, Boston, Massachusetts, November 24, 1944 (Box 3, Item 14)
  - Local 384, Teamsters, Norristown, Pennsylvania, December 1, 1940 (Box 3, Item 15)
  - Local 386, Teamsters, Stanislaus, Merced, and Mariposa, California, August 3, 1994 (Box 3, Item 16)
  - Local 390, Freight Drivers, Warehousemen, and Helpers, Miami and Vicinity, Florida, January 16, 1961 (Box 3, Item 17)
  - Local 392, Van Drivers, Furniture Warehousemen and Handlers, TV and Radio Appliance, Air Conditioning Service Men and Piano Movers, October 17, 1956 (Box 3, Item 18)
  - Local 395, Teamsters, Saskatchewan, December 13, 1966 (Box 3, Item 19)
  - Local 398, Ice, Oil, Construction, and Allied Workers, Rochester, New York, May 23, 1945 (Box 3, Item 20)
  - Local 418, Production, Maintenance, Automotive Sales, Servicemen and Allied Workers, Identical Jurisdiction of Joint Council 73, May 13, 2003 (Box 3, Item 21)
  - Local 419, Teamsters, Ontario, October 31, 1975 (Box 3, Item 22)
  - Local 420, Building Materials and Truck Drivers, Los Angeles, California, December 1, 1940 (Box 3, Item 23)
  - Local 422, Scrap Metal, Miscellaneous, Auto Wrecking and Smelting Drivers and Workers, Cuyahoga, Lake and Geauga Counties, Ohio, September 14, 1993 (Box 3, Item 24)
  - Local 423, Teamsters, Aurora, Illinois, December 1, 1940 (Box 3, Item 25)
  - Local 424, Chemical, Energy, and Allied Workers, Ontario, February 7, 1979 (Box 3, Item 26)
  - Local 428, Teamsters, Steubenville, Ohio, November 9, 1942 (Box 3, Item 27)
  - Local 429, Teamsters, Reading, Pennsylvania, December 1, 1940 (Box 3, Item 28)
  - Local 437, Teamsters, Haverhill, Massachusetts, August 15, 1933 (Box 3, Item 29)
  - Local 437, Teamsters, Haverville, Massachusetts, December 1, 1940 (Box 3, Item 30)
  - Local 444, Teamsters, Polk County, Florida, July 9, 1975 (Box 3, Item 31)
  - Local 445, Teamsters, Utica, New York, May 29, 1912 (Box 3, Item 32)
  - Local 450, Public Employees of Ohio, Ohio, April 1, 1984 (Box 3, Item 33)
  - Local 455, Teamsters, Dixon and Sterling, Illinois, March 23, 1943 (Box 3, Item 34)
  - Local 462, Taxi Drivers, Northern New Jersey, April 1, 1965 (Box 3, Item 35)
  - Local 464, Teamsters, British Columbia, November 2, 1973 (Box 3, Item 36)
  - Local 469, Teamsters, Perth Country, New Jersey, December 1, 1940 (Box 3, Item 37)
  - Local 485, Bakery Drivers, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, December 1, 1940 (Box 3, Item 38)
  - Local 486, Teamsters, Saginaw, Michigan, March 16, 1937 (Box 3, Item 39)
  - Local 486, Teamsters, Saginaw, Bay City, and Fifteen Counties in the Upper Peninsula, Michigan, October 12, 2011 (Box 3, Item 40)
  - Local 496, Taxi Cab, Bus, and Terminal Drivers, Boston, Massachusetts, April 28, 1941 (Box 3, Item 41)
  - Local 500, Food Drivers, Helpers, and Warehouse Employees, Philadelphia, New Jersey, April 19, 1968 (Box 4, Item 1)
  - Local 502, Philadelphia Association of School Administrators, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, October 31, 1986 (Box 4, Item 2)
  - Local 504, General Warehouse Workers, Shippers, Packers, Receivers, Stockworkers, Chauffeurs, Helpers, Taxicab and Funeral Drivers, Boston, Massachusetts, July 24, 1995 (Box 4, Item 3)
  - Local 507, Manufacturing, Processing, Assembling, and Installer Employees, Cuyahoga County, Ohio, August 11, 1966 (Box 4, Item 4)
  - Local 509, General Drivers, Warehousemen, and Helpers, South Carolina, June 26, 1970 (Box 4, Item 5)
  - Local 510, Manufacturing and Processing Employees, Orville, Ohio, August 11, 1966 (Box 4, Item 6)
  - Local 513, Import and Export, Moving and Storage Employees and Owner-Operators, Civil Service, Sanitation, General Vending, Allied Workers, Garage Parking and Service Station Employees and Allied Workers, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, March 3, 1976 (Box 4, Item 7)
  - Local 513, Teamsters Airline, Aerospace, and Comair Employees, Greater Cincinnati and Kentucky Airport, Ohio, October 25, 2002 (Box 4, Item 8)
  - Local 513, Teamsters Airline, Aerospace, and Comair Employees, Greater Cincinnati, Kentucky Airport, Ohio, and all Comair Flight Attendants except Florida, October 27, 2005 (Box 4, Item 9)
  - Local 515, Teamsters, Chattanooga, Tennessee, April 14, 1970 (Box 4, Item 10)
  - Local 517, Creamery Employees and Drivers, Madera, Fresno, Tulare and Kings Counties, California, June 26, 1968 (Box 4, Item 11)
  - Local 526, Teamsters, Rhode Island, May 6, 1968 (Box 4, Item 12)
  - Local 528, Teamsters, Georgia except Savannah and Brunswick, July 26, 1965 (Box 4, Item 13)
  - Local 532, General Construction, Quebec, October 21, 1991 (Box 4, Item 14)
  - Local 533, Teamsters, Reno, Nevada, September 17, 1943 (Box 4, Item 15)
  - Local 533, Teamsters, Reno, Nevada, January 26, 1988 (Box 4, Item 16)
  - Local 534, Teamsters, Sedalia, Missouri, March 6, 1946 (Box 4, Item 17)
  - Local 537, Milk, Bakery, Laundry, Sales Drivers, Dairy and Vending Employees, and Allied Workers, Colorado, March 16, 1981 (Box 4, Item 18)
  - Local 541, Building Material, Excavating, Heavy Haulers, Drivers, Helpers, and Warehousemen, Kansas City, Missouri, January 21, 1965 (Box 4, Item 19)
  - Local 543, Teamsters, Indiana, June 12, 1978 (Box 4, Item 20)
  - Local 550, Bakery Drivers, New York, New York, July 1, 1944 (Box 4, Item 21)
  - Local 550, Bakery Drvers, New York, New York, February 10, 1956 (Box 4, Item 22)
  - Local 550, Solidarity Charter to New York State AFL-CIO, New York, April 30, 2006 (Box 4, Item 23)
  - Local 552, Automotive Petroleum and Allied Industries, Kansas City, Missouri, June 8, 1951 (Box 4, Item 24)
  - Local 552, Automotive, Dairy, Mechanics and Service Employees, Drivers, Cashiers, and Warehouse, Kansas and Missouri, December 11, 1990 (Box 4, Item 25)
  - Local 554, Teamsters, Omaha, Nebraska, December 1, 1940 (Box 4, Item 26)
  - Local 556, Teamsters, Oregon, July 26, 1963 (Box 4, Item 27)
  - Local 558, Market, Produce, Warehouse, Frozen Food, and Cannery Workers, Buffalo, New York, June 26, 1953 (Box 4, Item 28)
  - Local 560, Teamsters, New Jersey, May 30, 2008 (Box 4, Item 29)
  - Local 563, General Drivers and Dairy Employees, Menasha and Neenah, Wisconsin, February 13, 1980 (Box 4, Item 30)
  - Local 564, Teamsters, Pennsylvania, December 17, 1964 (Box 4, Item 31)
  - Local 570, Warehouse Employees, Dairy, Bakery, Soft Drink, Laundry, Linen, General Sales Drivers and Allied Employees, Baltimore, Maryland, March 12, 1985 (Box 4, Item 32)
  - Local 571, Teamsters, Elysia, Ohio, April 28, 1937 (Box 4, Item 33)
  - Local 571, Teamsters, Lorain County, Ohio, October 16, 1951 (Box 4, Item 34)
  - Local 574, Teamsters, Cape Girard, Missouri, November 19, 1941 (Box 4, Item 35)
  - Local 576, Teamsters, Santa Clara and San Benino Counties, California, July 22, 1954 (Box 4, Item 36)
  - Local 578, Steel, Paper House and Chemical Drivers, Helpers and General Warehouse Workers, Los Angeles, California, October 27, 1998 (Box 4, Item 37)
  - Local 579, Teamsters, Janesville, Wisconsin, May 15, 1984 (Box 4, Item 38)
  - Local 579, Teamsters, Wisconsin, August 14, 1992 (Box 4, Item 39)
  - Local 580, Teamsters, Lansing, Michigan, December 1, 1940 (Box 4, Item 40)
  - Local 580, Teamsters, Lansing, Michigan, November 15, 2013 (Box 4, Item 41)
  - Local 581, Teamsters, Grand Forks, North Dakota, November 14, 1972 (Box 4, Item 42)
  - Local 598, Warehousemen, Los Angeles, California, December 1, 1940 (Box 4, Item 43)
  - Local 599, Warehouse, Food Processors, and Driver Sales Union, Tacoma and Pierce County, Washington, July 1, 1976 (Box 4, Item 44)
  - Local 599, Warehouse, Food Processors, and Driver Sales Union, Tacoma and Pierce County, Washington, April 11, 1985 (Box 4, Item 45)